{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565671802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565671802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565746367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565746366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565746445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565746445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 11799a3c-3512-4504-8546-7e2d93955a8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565766091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565766090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565769256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565769256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565773252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565773252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565801233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565801233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565816042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565816042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565826781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565826781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565830110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565830109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565833387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565833387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565838937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565838937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565848312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565848312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565851778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565851778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_B-R-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565858778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565858778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565862853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565862853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565866011","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565866011"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565869289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565869288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565872273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565872273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565876136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565876136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565881692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565881692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565885150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565885150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565888367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565888367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565891824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565891824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565895195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565895195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565902925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565902925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565911247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565911246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565915450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565915450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565920658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565920658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565934213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565934213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565942629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565942628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565948374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565948373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 16ff435e-a37a-47e1-b825-b29df02e4567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565957620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565957620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565964219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565964219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565969279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565969279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_17_17-3-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 17"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565975743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565975743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_17_17-3-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 17"," userResponse":" 17"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565980759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565980759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-11"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565986051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565986051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_11-7-15"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565991643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565991643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548565997388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548565997388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_8-7-15"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566002465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566002465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-9-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566008982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566008982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566019204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566019204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-4-14"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566025890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566025890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-4-14"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566031885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566031884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566038913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566038911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" f0c34ad0-ac24-485d-bf45-504700db39f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566050096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566050096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566052830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566052830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566054385","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566054384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566058168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566058168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566059728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566059728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566063915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566063915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566065489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566065488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566069444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566069444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566071017","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566071016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566075056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566075056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566076617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566076617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566079983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566079982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566081545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566081545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566085332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566085332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566086884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566086884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566092955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566092954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566094543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566094543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566097855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566097855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566099409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566099409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566103236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566103236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566104783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566104783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566108426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566108426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566110433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566110433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566110597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566110597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566118194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566118193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" ec061f04-9533-4774-a57e-8eb549bfe4a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566127438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566127438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_z-a-r"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566130576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566130576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_l-a-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566133850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566133850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_r-o-a"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566137279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566137279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_u-a-g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566141479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566141479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_g-a-t"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566144360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566144360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-z-w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566147206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566147206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-h-m"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566150052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566150052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-z"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566153302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566153302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-k-a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566156284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566156284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-s-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566162059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566162057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 009f8f58-bf71-4911-812d-24da5b8172fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-s-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566174479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566174479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_g-a-t"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566177463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566177463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566180523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566180523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_l-a-b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566184440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566184440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_r-o-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566187579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566187578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-h-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566190527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566190526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-s-l"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566193905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566193905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_z-a-r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566201123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566201123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-z-w"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566208529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566208529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_u-a-g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566211916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566211916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-k-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566217665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566217663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-k-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566224071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566224071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 6106cacd-9550-401e-9288-bd8a5fff4352"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.show.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-k-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566232368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566232368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-l"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566235532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566235532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_w-t-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566239622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566239622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_s-a-t"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566243054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566243054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_b-w-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566246045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566246045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-g"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566249652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566249652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_z-a-v"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566254047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566254047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_ch-k-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566258815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566258815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-ch-a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566263858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566263857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-ch-a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566268122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566268122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-ch-m"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566271285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566271284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_g-l-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566277031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566277030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_a_g-l-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566284443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566284443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 82b5f3f1-b682-47d0-9f55-9445effdee20"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_g-l-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566295375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566295374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566298065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566298065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566299610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566299610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566302588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566302588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566304144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566304144"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566307117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566307117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566308676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566308676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566311342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566311341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566312901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566312901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566315879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566315879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566317435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566317434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566320482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566320482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566322035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566322035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566324795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566324795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566326345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566326345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566329219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566329219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566330777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566330777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566334107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566334107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566335770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566335770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566335778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566335778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566364757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566364756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566364862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566364861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566372371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566372371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" a5643dc0-7227-41fc-9beb-f6b3192ff176"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566380930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566380930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566384214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566384214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566387490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566387490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566390773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566390772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566394459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566394459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566399270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566399270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566402614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566402613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566407416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566407416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566412003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566412003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566417697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566417697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566423252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566423252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566426366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566426366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566430163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566430163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566432960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566432960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566437143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566437143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566440290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566440290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566443455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566443455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566446645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566446645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566449843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566449843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566454087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566454087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566457320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566457320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566460261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566460261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566463762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566463762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566467816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566467815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566470646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566470646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566476406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566476405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566483024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566483024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" df66d6fe-31ce-4dc2-a6f0-a8d4c1fa0c83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566491945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566491945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 0ced5869-98ee-4f64-a543-e1d0cdffe06d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566492560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566492560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 0ced5869-98ee-4f64-a543-e1d0cdffe06d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566498179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566498179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 0ced5869-98ee-4f64-a543-e1d0cdffe06d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566508059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566508059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" BODABODA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566511737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566511737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bodaboda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BODABODA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566513286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566513286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" BENDERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566516692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566516692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bendera"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BENDERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566518247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566518247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566521620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566521620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566523177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566523177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566526412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566526412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566527967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566527967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566531349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566531349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" barabara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566532911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566532910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566536571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566536570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" buibui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566538130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566538129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566543341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566543341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baisikeli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566544901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566544901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566548129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566548129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566549692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566549692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" BEGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566553145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566553145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bega"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566554703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566554703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566558400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566558400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" basi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566559968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566559968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566559977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566559977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-B.rand.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566568739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566568738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566568830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566568830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" dc116656-7cc5-4062-a3ef-b036e6214426"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-B.rand.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566594949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566594949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 2004bd20-f6cd-4536-9e9e-a7c102e782ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566612053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566612053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 2004bd20-f6cd-4536-9e9e-a7c102e782ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566629364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566629364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 2004bd20-f6cd-4536-9e9e-a7c102e782ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566651104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566651103"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 2004bd20-f6cd-4536-9e9e-a7c102e782ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566651176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566651175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 2004bd20-f6cd-4536-9e9e-a7c102e782ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566660548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566660548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566660921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566660921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566661405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566661405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566661749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566661749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566662153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566662153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566662627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566662627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566662850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566662850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566666074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566666073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566666106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566666106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566666819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566666819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566667224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566667224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566667527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566667527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566667745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566667745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566667947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566667947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566668280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566668280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566668519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566668519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566671776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566671776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566672189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566672189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566674720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566674720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566674929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566674929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566675137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566675137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566678662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566678662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566682492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566682491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566683519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566683519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566686281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566686280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566686664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566686664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566687159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566687159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566687508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566687508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566687927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566687926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566688414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566688413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566688654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566688654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566691830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566691829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566691869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566691868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566692598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566692597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566693004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566693003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566693310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566693310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566693520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566693520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566693719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566693719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566694046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566694046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566694280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566694279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566696979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566696979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566697046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566697046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL2.incr.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566702294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566702294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 7d8ca177-987d-4b4f-803d-461ddec2fa2b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566710569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566710569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-o"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566713775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566713775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_y-w-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566716603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566716603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-u-b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566724505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566724505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-u-b"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566727803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566727803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_i-b-f"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566731105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566731105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_z-b-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566734372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566734372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-m-g"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566739951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566739951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_p-b-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566747391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566747391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-ch-m"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566752699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566752699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-y-s"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566755603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566755603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566761371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566761371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566767509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566767509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566773523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566773522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566779290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566779290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" 624b85f4-9f82-4011-9baf-93b260f345fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_B..B.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.81"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-i-p"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566789990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566789990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566794388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566794387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566796028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566796028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566799324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566799323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566800929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566800928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566804239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566804239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566805820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566805820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566810049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566810049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566811611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566811611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566816654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566816654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566818222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566818222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566821217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566821217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566822772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566822771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566825529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566825529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566827080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566827080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566829230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566829230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566830810","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566830810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566834273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566834273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566835836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566835836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566838858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566838858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566840404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566840404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566843928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566843928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566845486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566845486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566848736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566848736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566850290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566850290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566852943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566852943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566854546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566854546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566856796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566856796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566858384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566858384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566862065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566862065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" START_O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566864293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566864293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566865897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566865896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566868241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566868241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566869847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566869846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566872587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566872587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566874162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566874162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566876580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566876580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566878149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566878148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566880380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566880380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566881928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566881928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566884782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566884782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566886346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566886346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566889383","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566889383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566890972","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566890972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566893935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566893935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566895505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566895504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566898693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566898693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566900252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566900252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566903454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566903454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566905475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566905475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548566905636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548566905636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_080729"," gameId":" b68626cb-2bc4-4318-a506-152663ebcbd1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}